

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a UX-proficient UI Designer and Front-End Developer. I am passionate about design and enjoy the process of taking projects from simple ideas all the way through development. I obsess over details and pixel perfection and always stay mindful of the big picture.

I'm also an eager learner and am constantly striving to improve my own skills and abilities; my goal is to be a full-stack designer with proficiency in all three areas of expertise.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## TRUNK CLUB | Chicago, IL

### Front End Designer

February 2016 - Present

- Sole front end developer for Trunk Club website rebrand and design overhaul
- Worked with designers to rebrand and develop reusable templates for email marketing campaigns
- Developed reusable site templates using Statamic CMS
- Designed and developed microinteractions and animations

# **DESIGNATION** | Chicago, IL

### Designer-in-Residence

October 2015 - January 2016

- Led student stand-ups and advised students on project direction
- Advised students on design direction and front-end development
- Assisted with teaching efforts in the virtual phase of the program
- Designed and developed internal web pages with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

## UI Designer & Front-End Developer

May 2015 - September 2015

- Learned full-stack design and applied knowledge to mock and client projects
- Designed mobile and web applications using design thinking and agile methodology
- Developed responsive web applications and web pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and JavaScript libraries and frameworks (including Angular.js, D3.js, and jQuery)

### **EDUCATION**

## Northwestern University | Evanston, IL

B.A., Psychology

September 2011 - June 2015

### CONTACT

w: nelsonchang.me

e: nelsonschang@gmail.com

t: 214 457 4466

#### SOCIAL

🢶 github.com/neldotpng

instagram.com/nel.gif

in linkedin.com/in/nelsonschang

#### **SKILLS & EXPERTISE**

### **Proficient**

Photoshop	jQuery
llustrator	HTML5
Branding	CSS3
UI development	SASS
Wireframing	Git
nvision	AJAX
JavaScript	JSON

#### Intermediate

Statamic

Axure	Terminal
Research	ES6
InDesign	Angular.js
Mobile app design	D3.js
User testing	Python
Prototyping	CoffeeScript
Gulp	Sketch

### **Exploring**

React	Objective-C
Swift	·